Guide to The Edward Streeter Papers 1909-1976 MSS 39 MSS.039
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Printed Material
  - Subseries A: Printed Material.
    - Collier's Magazine: 1925: January 10 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_e3fdf28d3608f5b1db81819a991912c5)
    - Collier's Magazine: 1949: January 8-22 "Father of the Bride" (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_853847d27e6dbaa569ac622268813962)
    - Saturday Evening Post: 1920: July 24 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_4cd88d49f00911be079fdfa23e4c5ce0)
    - Saturday Evening Post: 1920.September 11 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_19cfda82b8667b6bd4d72a04bcb47d8a)
    - Saturday Evening Post: 1920.November 13 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_74e0ead4cc194f58295dc56b3e578ffb)
    - Saturday Evening Post: 1945: December 8 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_12bfb77de0ca5813179f662953a53c4b)
    - Metropolitan: Streeter, Edward. "Mary, Mary Quite Contrary. ", 1921-1922 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_5f954c5dc29c57fefa7ecec9ddcabedf)
    - Metropolitan: Streeter, Edward. "Over a Dead Man's Chest. ", 1921-1922 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_e42793fe7cf77f1f54b9c9992bd32c96)
    - Metropolitan: Fitzgerald, F. Scott. "The Beautiful and the Damned. ", 1921-1922 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_f8988153452c0de529b7a3f2a9777700)
    - Country Life: 1948: May; "Daily Except Sunday" Condensation (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_20b1f867338b80d80fd55c697396afad)
    - Good Housekeeping: 1954: May; "One Big Happy Family" (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_f4ecc0f0b594f7b4a89229ca868a6385)
    - Good Housekeeping: 1958: June; "Mr. Robbins Rides Again" (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_9a0364730a1860530b830753c1558d84)
    - Gas Attack, v. 1, nos. 1-4, 11, 14, 18-24., 1917-1918 (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_f47f52469a5e77f8da2867342e79bffc)
    - Life: 1962: September 14; "Don't Write Off Wisdom" (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_ad8c99dbeed5784dd8a72c8e0608be0e)
    - Boxoffice. 1950, August 12. (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_d1eed3537d4bd58004e645a2e76642a8)
    - SS France Passenger List: 1929, May 15. (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_0559c7b6db68cec7791e3c3e5a9cd661)
    - Poster (11 x 14); Ad for Father of the Bride [2 copies]., ca. 1950 (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_abbae1f0af0e339a82351c0ff8a8afbc)
    - Motion Picture Herald: 1950: May, Aug, Sept. "Father of the Bride" (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_35bd26e9818185fc2fdb054eebb606aa)
    - McCall's: 1963: June; "The Fourth Bride" (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_52fbd0dacfce16003af3499c9bdb10bb)
    - Omnibook: 1939: March; "Daily Except Sunday" [abridged] (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_97189ba77f99b54ff41d0a8b4822a9cf)
    - Book of the Month Club News, 1949, May; 1954, May; 1969, Fall., 1949-1969 (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_0bd5f58bbdf3f9b9ab18aa92c3b0c2fa)
    - Publishers Weekly, 1949, March. (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_3a25bc8aecbc6c811e566a33e81bf352)
    - Showplace (Radio City Music Hall Program). 1950, June 1. (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_e3cc94a339addc81e1a7af656b844a55)
    - The Guardsman, 1922, March 1. (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_9fbb92e560c82ae31c5bbf52451f38f2)
    - Yale Courant, 1915, October. (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_0574192b4866d34bd1dd4f3502f729d0)
    - Lotus Eaters/ Hasty Pudding Club, 1907 (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_b859575513f379e7d8be99da42ca7165)
    - New Yorker, [Manley, Jared L. "Where are They Now-"The New Yorker: June 26, 1937.] (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_11f984be7fc7b49121fba5174e327141)
    - Harvard Jubilee (Midyear, Reunion, and Christmas)., 1939 (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_c395c3056299c316c626ce6484d008d7)
    - The American Home, 1934, March. (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_8c0fd2150d4984bf4c6e81d3c0b23851)
    - Life at the 1914 Reunion (Harvard)., 1939 (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_b4f265e9a84785f5867ae9f1b28afd23)
    - Anonymous. "He Was Chairman of the Bored. "Retirement Planning News Service, Vol. 7, No. 4 [April 1962]. (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_953c36a0f4df0f2befc9bd5f04993a75)
    - The Log: 1950: Vol. 39, No. 10 Review of "Father of the Bride" (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_01a13eda692ff729a095171eb87241d4)
    - Bank One [Fall 1959]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_50918f3af3b918568a4d5ccd6b9d77fe)
    - Harper's: 1953: December. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_109913db69a7ae69dc818e04c9400540)
    - Homes and Gardens: 1962: December (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_88826c525898377acfd34584a3b1b836)
    - The White Book, 1932 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_7e127d4c140772f21874b5a58f82bacd)
    - Saturday Review, 1966, December 24. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_886de2ba5fa88a2093ed9e79dce8a184)
    - Popular Educator, 1940 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_0161f1db52b1ad5f6138e95ea3c988b1)
    - Newsweek, 1949, March 7. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_2acd8c00a011b7387b9ba10e213b4a52)
    - Redbook, 1932, December; 1933, February and March., 1932-1933 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_5f1c31cf1ab877056cbdf086c2cf3b85)
    - New York National Guardsman, 1924, April. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_a6e7e0e99fd78e687d8c7dd0f567b829)
    - The Literary Digest, 1924, February 16. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_7368f54ee37ccfcfed3b96a926a1fe23)
    - Harvard Today, 1958, December; 1961, Autumn., 1958, 1961 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_12ab74a957a8d90c87f96ba9b81b4314)
    - Harvard Club of New York Bulletin, 1971. (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_8f2b1f29df2d46b0f405795f285c5277)
    - Daily Variety, 1950 October 20. (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_b95fc44066e5d4b9d580dd4210161433)
    - The Harvard Foundation for Advanced Study and Research Newsletter, 1959, September 30. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_a847bf232754ac957906f832a3ba1e21)
    - Harvard Alumni Bulletin, 1953, December 12; 1951, March 24; 1948., 1948-1953 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_f0323b90aedd84b15d9ab68455a550fd)
    - 5 Pointer, 1956, March. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_3ecaf8122f3eaefebd8473d2dd52204a)
    - Harper's: 1953, December; 1956, October; 1954, March., 1953-1956 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_c318be0eaa0f894706374c1f8b832646)
    - Redbook: Vol 60, No. 6; Vol. 61, No. 4, 2-4 [1932-33]., 1932-1933 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_b021e4e5f58230a490b27767cfbef6a3)
    - Redbook: Vol. 64, No. 6 [Apr. 1935]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_1c1463fa8357e7c7208abf5a50f9634d)
    - Redbook: Vol. 74, No. 4 [Feb. 1940]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_f31d66f1688d558762abd858b72d125e)
    - Redbook: Vol. 77, No. 2 [June 1941]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_3a25a80bc02a611f7b78912e99a242c1)
    - Redbook: Vol. 78, No. 1 [Nov. 1941]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_3496aed2e9a88e9ea9ac9184c9fc24c5)
    - Redbook: Vol. 79, No. 3-4 [July-Aug. 1942]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_a6445036f841aa44cb249691dec24c1b)
    - Redbook: Vol. 81, No. 1 [May 1943]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_90620715409b4bf65fc77f9cd3f0dca9)
    - Redbook: Vol. 85, No. 3 [July 1945]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_c63c90bd1666543e842a4fcbd459b521)
    - The Writer: 1958: September"Old Story, New Style. " (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_dbe70290de46534386d4007a58f9ebaf)
    - Reader's Digest. "Father of the Bride. ": 1938: December [English Language]. (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_4182b7efabf92890776d971b57ee51f6)
    - Reader's Digest. "Father of the Bride. ": 1949-50: October-December [Multi-language Issues]., 1949-1950 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_562edf566ede60f4c0ab1b6e06080417)
    - Harvard Lampoon [numerous issues], 1908-1914, 1916, 1924, 1951 (Box 24, Folder data_value_missing_7f8abecbc368afb0e687951a4d0a1e74)
  - Subseries B: Scrapbooks & Pictorial [SB=Scrapbook]
    - Father of the Bride Scrapbook., undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_078df25297387b86a5c765dc1aaaafb7)
    - The Log of the Trade Wind [1926]. (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_677195d625fe781b166a02ddeeda1488)
    - The Pontefract, 1908-1910. (Box 28, Folder data_value_missing_a6e1ebd08bbc9ccb97328389df704728)
    - Pomfret, 1910. (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_ce0c196413ea12169d547a5cd7675600)
    - General Scrapbooks (2), undated (Box 25, Folder data_value_missing_deddb659a26c5d0c9a7abd0bf303fead)
    - Bill Breck Drawings, undated (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_a36d8cd58f0b77367acd5ad75519e6ff)
    - World War I Era Photos [1915]; [2] Panoramic shots of New York cavalry regiment drilling in Poughkeepsie, NY. (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_2c5fbbeecced5167d027d271ebac36d1)
  - Subseries C: Oversized
    - Illustration by Don Carlisle for Redbook article on dogs., undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_68a60d821b5ae52646b25569286a4ff8)
    - The Pontefract [1950, 1955) (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_3a5ae2b807d1e62f6e324a6b9f3a0918)
    - Smith, Isobel/Tuberculosis, Life Magazine [Dec. 27, 1954] (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_edb3c085f43638e9634b310327977d6d)
    - Washington Square Journal [Nov. 2, 1964] (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_c02dcacc4175af21d386fbffcc65b502)
    - Articles A-H: Don't Write Off Wisdom The Great Outdoorsman Have Fathers Changed- How to Guess Your Age by Corey Ford, undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_63bf207329973f5d5a4e7ffe791afe95)
    - I-R: I'll Remember it in a Minute by Corey Ford; Pleasant Scandinavia..., undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_bb59cf0238466536aba077eb879a8e85)
    - S-V: Today is Your Day 'Twas the Night Before Christmas, undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_b6620765bd01ebb0b2df5bba2550485b)
    - W-Z: Wedding Pests, undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_2c5c9d3437f5d7f16073dc4d37ed3744)
    - What Did They Give Walt Whitman for Christmas-, undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_f029fa21b76ea2ceb6512321b1fdf87b)
    - Why Grandpa Can't Read, undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_54c574bd30dd6b1e09a90de8290d45cb)
    - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 29, Folder data_value_missing_f959ea5b71391c5a029dd020e512b4f1)